= kisskh.asia =
♪ From primal chaos to the starry sky ♪
♪ In the whole world, we shall hold the balance ♪
♪ The cauldron tempers divine blades ♪
♪ The furnace refines the empty void ♪
♪ The Way is in mystic fate ♪
♪ Be brave enough to split the primal chaos wide open ♪
[Pull Strings]
[Adapted from the novel by Yan Gui Zheng Zhuan]
[Episode 22]
At that time, I was barely conscious.
I could only entrust this great undertaking
to you and Jiu Wu.
You two
truly united the Three Sects.
I am truly gratified.
Senior.
Senior,
is it because.
I didn't persuade Aunt Jiu Jiu to come
that Uncle Jiu Wu.
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
Mentor was worried about us,
so he had Uncle Jiu Wu look after us.
You can never truly know someone's heart.
Uncle Jiu Wu.
I'll play weiqi with you
in the next life.
You promised me you'd come back.
Liar.
I was the one supposed to go.
The one who should have died was me.
Why you?
Get up.
Get up!
I am deeply ashamed.
The pearl of our sect
can actually be used like this.
Changgeng,
what spell did you just use?
That's one of my Montage Art tricks.
It's called
the CAG special effect.
It can add new content at will
in this pearl image,
turning it into an illusion.
Montage...
CAG?
An illusion?
The world's magic
is truly ever-changing.
I am again enlightened.
Changgeng,
your mastery is so profound.
Why don't you do it yourself?
Why use my hands for this illusion?
I'm a carefree wandering immortal,
dragged into this mess for no reason,
already entangled in too much karma.
The credit for resolving the crisis of the Three Sects
shall go to you.
Indifferent to fame and fortune,
and of remarkable attainment.
I've learned much today.
Then I must trouble you as well.
As you've seen for yourself,
this has nothing to do with our sect.
It's that Westdawn causing all the trouble.
Please pass word to your sect's sage.
Of course, of course.
Many thanks.
Hermit,
what of the item I entrusted to you?
I'm ashamed.
I couldn't tell what treasure it was,
but it drew hordes of demons from all around.
They swarmed me.
I couldn't hold them off alone.
What do you mean?
You didn't lose it, did you?
Why didn't you lose yourself too?
I've had it.
I've wronged you, Changgeng.
I willingly accept punishment.
Forget about punishment.
What good is punishing you now?
You lost his stuff.
Pay 50,000 spirit stones.
How much?
Or give me that pearl instead.
Hermit, do not blame yourself.
The pearl.
I have
foreseen this.
To gain, there must be loss.
Since loss is inevitable,
why not turn this loss to advantage?
Westdawn Sect wants the Pregenesis Sword.
That's why they attacked Ascendance Sect.
But little do they know
that I only have one fragment.
So, they must seek the other two fragments.
Thus...
We can surely lure them out.
Wait.
Since you want to discard it,
why make me guard it?
How did you even become an immortal?
If we leave it for someone to take,
isn't that obviously a trap?
Your guarding it makes the ruse more real.
I'm speechless.
It really is.
The traitor Kuai Si said
that Westdawn Sect is set up in the East Sea.
They'll soon trigger the Great Tribulation.
We must lure them out asap.
Then what are we waiting for?
Let's charge into the East Sea now.
No, no.
The East Sea is the Dragon Clan's territory.
If you just storm in there,
it'll surely spark a human-dragon war.
That would make things far worse.
Then what do you suggest?
Ascendance Sect has long had ties with the Dragon Palace.
We need only send a small team inside
to root out the hidden mastermind.
Then, we can avert the Great Tribulation.
You're humans.
Will they let you enter
without reason?
Don't worry.
I still hold a hidden trump card.
Greetings, Grandlord.
The Sea Deity Sect
is vast in territory, with countless disciples,
but I roam afar, hard to govern.
To ensure the Sea Deity Sect endures forever,
today,
I formally declare
the appointment
of Ao Yi, Second Prince of the East Sea,
as the Second Grandlord
and Azure Protector
to act as Grandlord.
I...
How could I deserve this?
No need to refuse.
I saw you turn into a golden dragon,
fight off the demons,
and save everyone.
You are already a great hero.
I...
Am I already a great hero?
I know
you've always dreamed of leading
the Dragon Clan back to glory.
That's right.
Then, now
is the time.
You can return to the Dragon Palace
as the Second Grandlord
and the Azure Protector.
Then, your father and brother
will see how strong you've grown
after what you've been through.
Yes, Grandlord.
This time,
I will crush Westdawn Sect's plot
to pieces.
As expected of Changgeng.
You're nothing like what I heard.
You heard about me?
What did you hear about me?
I heard it from my sister.
She said you dodge trouble when you can
and are selfish, given to despair,
wallow in self-pity,
and...
You know what I mean.
But seeing you today,
you truly have a heroic air.
My sister's view is too shallow.
You're right.
The old Changgeng
would never have formulated
a plan to strike first.
I used to think
that everything was under my control
and that everything in this world
would unfold as I envisioned.
But I was wrong.
My avoidance
only let those demons run wilder,
causing irreparable harm.
From this day forward,
I will no longer hide.
Even if the Great Tribulation arrives,
I will also give it a try.
I will show Fate
that the Great Tribulation
does not come and go as it pleases.
Mentor,
sorry
about the Transformation Art.
You've worked so hard.
Rest for a while.
My heart is now empty.
Nothing left at all.
Sit with me for a while.
Not yet.
The sect must escort the Second Prince back.
The Second Prince named me
to accompany him.
I never knew you were this busy.
No, wait.
You were busy before too,
but I never knew what kept you so occupied.
Go on.
After all, I used to be alone
in Jade Division.
I can endure this loneliness.
Go on.
This jade talisman had Kuai Si's demonic arts.
Kuai Si is dead.
So, the demonic arts are dispelled.
♪ See mortal joys and sorrows ♪
♪ Reunions and partings, as fate unfolds ♪
♪ Alas, love has many twists and turns ♪
♪ Memories filled with sorrow ♪
♪ Slowly, wishes turn to regret ♪
Junior Qi Yuan,
since I left without saying goodbye,
it's been many years.
Is all well in Jade Division?
Mentor and I are in Kuru Land,
seeking herbs to restore your foundation.
Mortals always envy us cultivators
for having a path to eternal life.
A thousand years pass in a blink for us.
But they do not know this:
Even parted mortals feel each day is a year.
How can separated cultivators
bear a thousand years of longing?
So what if we have magic power?
So what if we can live long?
Sometimes, I think
it's fine to trade for a few decades together.
Set out.
With these cultivation bodies
of ours.
[Hall of Mystic Truth]
Whenever I think of this,
I lie awake at night.
But then I think
once I've restored your foundation,
we can be together for eons.
Wouldn't that be even more beautiful?
Kuru Land is perilous,
yet some corners are truly breathtaking.
At times, I think
that if we both ascended,
I'd surely bring you here,
and we'd be wandering immortals together.
Could such a day come?
Junior,
I will surely return.
However long it'll take,
I'll return someday.
So,
you must stay alive
and wait for me.
If you dare lose heart
and abandon this cultivation path,
I will not forgive you.
Senior,
I'll remember you.
You'll always be in my heart.
♪ Slowly, wishes turn to regret ♪
♪ You've gone afar, like mist fading ♪
[Hall of Mystic Truth]
♪ Past fragments ♪
♪ Vanish into night ♪
[Jade Division]
My Blood Gnats
have been completely wiped out?
Defeated Wen Jing,
do you admit your guilt?
I'm Wen Jing.
Greetings, Two Saints of Westdawn.
[Jieyin, Saint of Westdawn Sect] You've failed to seize...
[Zhunti, Saint of Westdawn Sect] The Pregenesis Sword.
Sorry for being incompetent.
Incompetent?
The army was dispatched, yet all efforts were in vain.
You have sabotaged our sect's grand plan.
What punishment do you deserve?
I failed in proper planning.
I'm unforgivable!
Yet Ascendance Sect was gravely wounded.
Seizing and Human Sects became sworn foes.
I think...
Foolish!
Arrogant!
You think your petty puppetry spell
can fool Voidcity?
We covered for you,
yet you exposed yourself.
Voidcity has likely noticed you.
Our sect now faces exposure.
Should the Three Sects investigate,
our sect may not withstand it.
Now, we can only
kill the demons to prove our innocence.
No, no!
Please, no!
No!
I'm begging you.
I committed the guilt
and wrongs alone.
Should punishment come,
I will bear it all.
I beg you to grant this.
Too late.
I've already destroyed three-tenths
of your clan left in the Blood Sea.
I also destroyed
another three-tenths.
The Two Saints of Westdawn punish the wicked
to avenge the Ascendance Sect.
Thus,
the Three Sects won't doubt us.
The fate of the remaining
four-tenths of your clan
depends on your future conduct.
You must understand
that all this karma
stems from your crushing defeat today.
Thanks
for your grace.
I will not disappoint you again.
Go to the East Sea at once.
Meet Jin Chan there.
Jin Chan has the Pregenesis Sword.
The Eye of the East Sea
will open soon.
[When the demons attacked Ascendance Sect.]
Lie down.
A python swallowed you.
You were nearly destroyed.
Luckily,
you met me.
You cannot speak
and have no memory.
When I found you, you were barely alive.
From now on,
we'll call you Cansheng.
Who are you?
The sea of suffering is endless.
Turn back, and you'll find the shore.
You lost the Pregenesis Sword?
The situation was critical.
Only the Sword fragment could bait them.
It was our only way to survive.
You gave me your word
that your fragment would be safe.
They came for the Sword.
If all three fragments were in the Celestial Court,
the Westdawn Sect would attack directly.
The aftermath would be unimaginable.
That's not wrong.
We barely have forces.
We couldn't hold it.
Thanks for the warning.
I'll hide
my fragment carefully.
Actually,
I've come for your fragment.
Ascendance Sect had this battle
because we were
too conservative in strategy.
Even the strongest defense
can't hold against repeated attacks.
That's true.
Since the enemy openly aims for the Sword,
we should turn defense into offense
and end this threat for good.
So, you deliberately let the Demon Clan
take the Sword fragment.
Though Westdawn Sect hasn't surfaced,
they must have already slipped into the Dragon Palace.
This is our only chance to flush them out.
Once Westdawn Sect sees that fragment,
they will...
They'll seek out the other fragments.
Your Majesty, you're wise.
I happen to have a fragment.
How wise of you.
I can lure them out,
reveal their true, ugly faces,
and catch them all in one sweep.
Exactly.
You want me to give you the fragment?
The Sword has three fragments.
Even if the Westdawn Sect seizes two fragments,
they still can't
unlock its original power
to open the Eye of the East Sea.
Therefore,
as long as Fairy Yunxiao's fragment is safe,
risking my fragment is acceptable.
You are right.
Still, it's a little risky.
I will devise a solid plan.
And I will ensure everything
goes exactly according to plan.
This plan hardly seems your doing.
Aren't you known for playing it safe?
I just think
that one
should sometimes try
something a bit risky.
[Li Changshou]
Connect! Connect!
This is so serious.
Connect!
Should we bring Fairy Yunxiao in
to help us out?
No.
We're already risking
two fragments.
We must not involve her further.
We even need to control her whereabouts
to keep her from showing up.
Connect!
[Fairy Yunxiao] Connect!
That's Fairy Yunxiao.
She appears and vanishes without a trace.
Even Heaven reach Master
can't find her.
You used to find her all the time, right?
Now that you mention it,
every time she came to me before,
it was her Resonance that summoned me.
I've never actively gone looking for her.
Maybe she's left some Resonance
for you in some remote corner?
I don't think so.
But
that's just as well.
If we can't find her, we'll avoid her.
It'll have the same effect.
So, you're planning
to never see her again?
Between you and Fairy Yunxiao,
what happened?
Nothing.
During the crisis at Ascendance Sect,
Fairy Yunxiao stormed my Hall of Soaring Heaven.
She summoned the Grand Mage of Voidcity.
She said
she won't contact you anymore.
So be it.
With her out of the way,
we can now carry out
our East Sea plan.
You two argued.
Fairy Yunxiao is such an important person.
I...
How could a lowly disciple like me
ever rein her in?
I simply want her to be free,
far from all turmoil.
That would satisfy me.
Your Majesty, may I speak?
I have another request.
This East Sea plan
will inevitably clash with Westdawn Sect.
I need many more weapons and instruments.
None.
I haven't even finished.
How would you know there aren't any?
Really, there's none.
The Celestial Court is vast.
There must be some instruments.
You're being so stingy!
Hand them over!
There were some before.
Now, they're gone.
What do you mean?
That's impossible.
You must have some.
Why would I lie?
Didn't Fairy Yunxiao come by once?
So what if she came by?
The Court's weapons and magic instruments
were all taken.
All taken?
Yeah.
Take what?
Who's trying to take things again?
Only one way in or out of the Dragon Palace.
If a fire broke out,
we'd be trapped.
You fool.
The Dragon Palace is all water.
How could there be a fire?
That's true.
[Token] It's all part of His Majesty's plan.
Without the Dragon Gate Token,
no one can invade our East Sea.
Who'd dare attack the East Sea?
Tell me.
We'll go report
the Little Prince's return.
If His Majesty is pleased,
might he grant us a reward?
Maybe.
[Token]
Alright.
Drink.
Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
You two.
Turtle.
Your Majesty.
Perfect timing. Come, come.
Drink with me.
I'll pass for now.
Urgent report, Your Majesty!
The Second Prince is back.
Second Prince?
What's this "second"?
How many sons do I have?
Your Majesty, your second son, Ao Yi.
He's back.
Exactly.
Ao Yi?
Yes, yes!
No, he barely left.
So, he couldn't handle it outside
and came back?
Yes.
It looks like Yi
still hasn't grown up.
Your Majesty!
Do you all know what day it is?
The Second Prince is coming back.
It's a joyful day, a good thing.
So cheer up, everyone.
Smile, smile!
When you play later,
give it your all.
Make my little brother happy.
Father.
The band is all ready.
The Little Prince is young, after all.
It's his first time out. Setbacks are inevitable.
A little dragon, first time out.
What majesty could he have?
Back when I was out there,
I endured so many hardships.
Father.
Things are not like your time anymore.
No matter how much he suffered outside,
as long as he comes back home,
we'll shower him with love.
He's our little treasure, after all.
Little treasure.
The little treasure's here.
He's here! Play the music!
He's back!
Stop the music!
Stop, stop!
Yi.
- No.
- Your Majesty!
- You're back.
I've missed you so much.
Your Majesty, this isn't...
Wrong, wrong.
Wrong.
Yi.
Your Majesty, Your Majesty.
Yi is not so chubby.
My Yi.
How did you get so round, Yi?
What on earth have you been eating
to end up like this?
Greetings, Dragon King.
Who are you?
Hello, everyone.
We are of the Sea Deity Sect.
By order of our Grandlord,
we are escorting Ao Yi, Second Grandlord
and Azure Protector,
back to the East Sea.
The Sea Deity Sect?
Second Grandlord?
Azure Protector?
Isn't this the East Sea?
What is the Sea Deity Grandlord?
How come I've never heard of him?
Our Grandlord is called.
Changgeng the Great.
Changgeng?
Changgeng again.
Here it comes again!
Here it comes!
Music! Music!
Stop.
Yi, my boy.
- Yi, you're finally back!
- That's my...
Your Majesty.
I've missed you dearly.
Your Majesty, your Majesty.
Wrong again, wrong again!
- What's wrong?
- Your Majesty.
It's wrong again.
How did he become a woman?
It's been so long, and Yi is a woman.
Greetings, Dragon King.
You...
Didn't you break off our betrothal?
So, you are no longer one of us.
Then why are you here today?
Today, I'm not
your follower.
I am Ao Yi's personal guard.
Personal?
Guard?
Personal guard?
By order of Grandlord Changgeng,
we brought the Little Prince home.
Changgeng again.
Second Prince Ao Yi's strength
has earned our warriors' respect.
From this day on,
the Mermaid Clan will follow him
and join the East Sea.
Good.
The more, the merrier.
What's so great? She...
Here it comes again.
Don't worry.
Watch my cue, play slowly.
Stop.
Still not right.
Yi... Yi...
Wrong again.
Wrong again?
Come on.
Must you be everywhere?
By the order of Grandlord Changgeng,
the Ascendance envoy is here
to escort Ao Yi - Envoy?
Back to the Dragon Palace.
This place
is Ao Yi's home.
Does he need you to escort him?
Days ago, demons besieged Ascendance Sect.
The Little Prince defeated demons as a golden dragon.
He did great deeds for us.
To show sincerity...
A golden dragon?
We brought gifts
to resolve human-dragon enmity.
Ao Yi turned
into a golden dragon?
Wake up, he's here.
Who's here?
He's here!
He's really here!
Play faster, play faster!
Get excited!
Your Majesty, Your Majesty!
He's really here this time.
Who's here?
The Second Prince.
Yi.
- You're finally back!
- Father.
Do you know how much I've missed you?
Father.
I ran away from home,
causing you such worry.
Please, punish me, Father.
What matters is you're home safe.
That's what matters.
No matter what hardships
you endured out there,
now that you're back,
no one will dare bully you again.
Father,
I've found a way
to restore our clan's former glory.
You've found a way?
Come.
Look.
This time,
we'll have to foil Westdawn Sect's plot
and complete
the Dragon Clan's ascension plan.
So, the Celestial Court must step in
to resolve the Dragon Clan crisis.
Then, I'll pin the credit
on you.
And the Dragon Clan
will naturally
and willingly come over to your side.
Great idea!
Then, I'll descend to the East Sea
as the Celestial Emperor.
Are you crazy?
If you go to the East Sea,
they'll think it's a coup and rebel.
What then?
Well, what do you suggest?
Well.
I think
we need someone else
to stand for the Celestial Court.
But this person
must be honest, obedient, and discreet.
They can vanish for ten or so days
without anyone noticing.
And the key thing is
they must fit the public's image
of a deity:
white hair, white brows, white beard
flowing robes, and wide sleeves.
I am Moon Elder, envoy of the Celestial Emperor.
By the order of Grandlord Changgeng...
Changgeng again.
I'm here to congratulate the return of Prince Ao Yi.
Your Majesty, Your Majesty!
An immortal envoy!
Oh, an immortal envoy.
So, the immortal envoy is here.
My apologies. Forgive me.
Yi,
it's such a big event.
Why didn't you tell me beforehand?
Turtle,
prepare a feast! A grand feast!
No, no!
I can't drink.
Come on, please.
I can't drink; I already threw up!
Please, please!
No way!
Not again?
Yi,
how many people did you bring back today?
I...
How many should I have brought today?
I have no idea!
Yunxiao.
Fairy Yunxiao.
Fairy Yunxiao, nice to meet you.
What brings you back
to the East Sea?
Sent by Grandlord Changgeng,
I'm here to escort the Prince Ao Yi
back to the Dragon Palace.
You're all sent
by Grandlord Changgeng
to escort my son?
Is that so?
I have a question, though.
Please enlighten me.
Who is Changgeng?
This is hardly a return.
Clearly, he's back to flaunt
his authority
before Father and me.
So, he covets my position as the Crown Prince.
To think I cared so much for his safety.
Ao Yi.
He...
He's a jerk!
Grandlord Changgeng of the Sea Deity Sect.
Your Highness,
do you still remember that name?
Changgeng.
How could I forget that name?
All my failures
are thanks to him.
I want revenge.
I'll kill him.
The battle in the South Sea was costly.
You haven't recovered yet.
For now, just rest and recuperate.
Don't bother
with everything else.
Right.
Don't bother with it.
Master Jin Chan,
the Sea Deity Sect...
Ao Yi's return now
is no coincidence.
It's Changgeng's scheme.
He's come to avenge Ascendance Sect.
♪ See mortal joys and sorrows ♪
♪ Reunions and partings, as fate unfolds ♪
♪ Alas, love has many twists and turns ♪
♪ Memories filled with sorrow ♪
♪ Slowly, wishes turn to regret ♪
♪ You've gone afar, like mist fading ♪
♪ Tearfully, this life's bond is not over ♪
♪ Past fragments vanish into night ♪
♪ Down a few more cups of wine ♪
♪ Through land and sea, I ask you to come ♪
♪ For honor's sake, upright and grand ♪
♪ Alas, our story is short ♪
♪ Slowly, wishes turn to regret ♪
♪ You've gone afar, like mist fading ♪
♪ Tears fall, this fate's not done ♪
♪ Past fragments vanish into night ♪